# SHUBHI MANGLA

Date Of Birth: 23/07/1997

Contact

Tel: 9953683031

e-mail:shubhimangla@gmail.com

#### **Address**

### 122A/3 GAUTAM NAGAR, NEW DELHI-110016

## **Objective**

Looking forward to join an organization where I can nurture my skills and enhance my knowledge in media industry, while working in an experience rich and competitive environment so that it is mutually beneficial to both myself and employer and allow for future growth and advancement.

## **Experience**

## **Job Experience**

## • Client Serving Intern | MullenLowe Lintas

December 2019- March 2019

- Handled the account of Havells India
- Coordinating with the design team and the client
- Releasing Artworks

### Social Media Intern

Socioar | November 2019 - December 2019

- Handling daily posting for brands like Dainik Jagran, The Lily Factory
- Content creation for Perenne, The Lily Factory
- Writing Blogs
- > Help in branding strategies for pitches
- Creating monthly social media reports

## Social Media Manager

Perfect Perception Media Pvt. Ltd | May 2018 - November 2018

- Handled social media platforms for the company including Facebook, Instagram and LinkedIn.
- > Designing campaigns and carousel ads on Facebook.
- Creating content for daily posts
- Generating leads on Facebook
- Coordinating with the designer for posts

#### 1 month Internship at Doordarshan –DD News

- News Operations
- Broadcast Engineering
- Programme Production
- New Media Cell

#### News Desk Intern

The Asian Age | June 2016- July 2016

- Editing News Copy
- Basics of Pagemaking
- Graphic designing for newspaper

## • Content Writing and Editorial Intern

Newsgram | March 2016- June 2016

- Writing Features and editing articles
- Scooping for topics and news
- > Sharing content on different online platforms
- > SEO optimization on Wordpress
- Uploading content on Wordpress

## • 1 month Internship at godoctr.com as a content writer

Blog writing

## **Academic Qualification**

- Certification Course in Digital Marketing from National Institute of Internet Marketing (NSIM)
- Completed Bachelors in Journalism & Mass Communication from Jagannath International Management School, Vasant Kunj affiliated to Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University
- Schooling from Father Agnel School, New Delhi
- Passed higher senior secondary in Commerce with Math stream from C.B.S.E, 2015 scoring 88.75%
- Passed Senior Secondary Certificate from C.B.S.E, 2013 scoring CGPA 8.0

## **Skills and Accomplishment**

- Knowledge of Word Press
- MS Office: Proficiency in MS Word & MS PowerPoint
- Knowledge of QuarkXPress, Adobe PageMaker, Adobe Indesign & Adobe Photoshop
- Blogging & Content writing
- Social Media Marketing/ Digital Marketing
- Participated in Commerce Olympiad in school
- Participated in Green Olympiad in School
- Third Position in Newsletter Designing in college
- Third Position in Short Film & Documentary making in college
- Volunteered for an event called 'Radio Mathematics' organized by JIMS in which villagers were educated about the importance of mathematics.
- Volunteered for Ladli Foundation & Trust, an NGO working for women empowerment with support from Delhi Police

- Movies
- Music
- Reading
- Animals
- Travel
- Writing

# Strengths

- Team Work
- Fast Learner
- Honest
- Sincere
- Positive Thinking
- Creative Approach
- Dedicated and Passionate about Work

## **Personal details**

Mother's name : VEENU MANGLA

Sex : FEMALE
Nationality : INDIAN
Age : 21 years

Language known : ENGLISH & HINDI

Religion : HINDU